does some great stuff off schedule. You
see the, you know, the way that Pard can
run when he gets behind his pads and
he's obviously dynamic and explosive,
but really pleased to be able to get the
win. I thought a lot of guys
contributed. Um, and that's where you
can see the depth of our football team.
We'll enjoy this. It'll make for a fun
flight home and then uh what a great
challenge we've got against Philly next
week.
>> Is this the kind of impact?
>> Yeah, I think so. You know, and I think
there's going to be some cool learning
ops for us as well. You know, we had a
couple things in the red zone where want
to be able to connect, but um you know,
he had a good a bunch of good catch and
runs. Makes another unbelievable catch
on an inb break, you know, when we're
kind of in a second down situation, but
thought the touchdown was big. You know,
we had him on a little double move in
the fringe, good late hands, and um I
thought he was excellent today. Um I
believe he went over 100, got his
touchdown, but and Puka just, you know,
what a stud. I mean, he's so critical in
in crunch time situations, whether it's
the fourth and one with a 45 yardd
touchdown run, well blocked play, he
ends up breaking the tackle, the safety,
um, and then really in the drive that we
felt like the game kind of opened up,
uh, two plays in a row to start, you
know, to be able to, um, you know, lead
to explosives. Uh, it was it was good.
And then, um, you know, I was pleased
with our team overall. But the answer is
yes, Adam.
>> Yeah, they just saw the way that he got
up, you know, it was that was buzzed
down. That wasn't from anybody, you
know, they were just being smart. Um, he
was kind of just, you know, a little bit
on the ground a little bit longer than
usual and and I think, you know, Aaron
on the side of safety and caution and so
he's good though.
>> Uh, he got his clavicle. He broke his
clavicle. So, it's unfortunate. Um, it's
a big loss. I thought Darius Williams
came in and made what a clutch break up
that he had on the third down to get us
off the grass. Um, Forbes and Dobe
continue to take steps in the right
direction. I was really pleased with our
defense. I thought it was awesome for D
will to be ready. Uh we said that we're,
you know, we've got four starting
corners. We feel that way. I feel
terrible for Aello. Um love him. It's
such a bummer. Um but you do feel
fortunate to have the depth where, you
know, a guy like D will can step up um
to be able to supplement both uh the
Kobe and uh and Forbes.
>> What have you seen in the first two
games that gives you confidence going up
against?
>> Well, I think we got a lot of work to
do. You know, I I feel good that we're
two and0, Gary. And um you know, I'll
look at the tape. uh we'll have a lot of
things that we can correct, but I
thought the second half, you know, you
talk about being able to put it together
on both sides and then in the kicking
game as well, that felt like when you
can put it all together, what it can
look like, um where you can be in
control and command of a game and that's
what it felt like. Uh we were really,
you know, starting kind of midway
through the third and then into the
fourth quarter. Um but we've got a great
challenge. We know what a great
atmosphere and environment, reigning
champs. Um, you know, I think, uh, they
play Kansas City later this afternoon,
so it' be fun to be able to watch it as
long as the damn Wi-Fi on the plane
works.
>> So,
>> it better work.
>> Ended up being a big game for Stafford,
but he did have that interception in the
second quarter. What is it about him
that shake off?
>> Mental toughness, resilience,
experience, um, you know, all the things
that lead to great players being great.
You show me a great player, I'll show
you a guy that's consistently overcome
adversity and setbacks. And so, um, you
know, it was a tough situation. I could
have had a better I could have put him
in a better spot. Um, he never flinches.
He was disappointed because of the spot
he put our team in where you're down,
um, you know, three points right there.
But you talk about a guy just doing what
he can and doing the next right thing
and he was in total command in the
second half. I thought he threw the ball
with great anticipation. Um, you know,
they did a good job of be able to
present some different pressure looks.
Uh, but he found his guys and got the
ball where he was supposed to. I think
it's almost good sometimes because of
the way that he's capable of responding,
but he's a total stud.
>> He was awesome. That was much more in
alignment. I thought Ron did a great
job, but we got two backs we feel really
good about and a guy in Jarquest Hunter
that's only going to get better. And so,
um, and then, you know, you talk about a
lot of good individual efforts by our
rookies, by some younger players. I was
really pleased with Blake. thought the
little gap run that he had on the second
down and 10 where he got through the
backside a gap, you know, looked like he
was going to come out clean. He's
explosive. Um, you know, he's he's he's
a good football player. I have a lot of
trust in him. And then, uh, you know,
we'll continue to see that moving
forward. So, I thought that was good
today. Sarah, also want to give a shout
out to Terrence Ferguson. What an
individual play when we got the extra
point blocked to not allow them to be
able to get two right there. Um, you see
the athleticism, be able to track that
down. He's a guy we want to be able to
keep get going. Uh, but I thought Higgby
did a nice job today as well as Davis
Allen.
>> Yep. Now, I'll say that against this
one, too. What did you think?
>> Well, I I would agree. I just How would
you describe that?
>> Same. I thought he took his game to the
next level. Um, you know, I thought his
just pursuit. You see when when Ward's
able to extend plays, he's got the speed
to be able to track him down. I think he
made the game-changing play uh where he
forces the sack fumble, but um his
presence, you know, I think our outside
back room, you know, Jared does such a
great job as well, but those two guys uh
they impose their will. They set edges
in the run game. They can be able to
create uh whether it's some of the
movements or whether it's winning on
individual rush situations. Uh Byron
Young was outstanding. It was cool to be
able to give him a game ball. He said it
was the first one. Uh so I've been
shortening him for a couple times
because he's deserved it before uh in
the locker room actually instead of
waiting until uh you know, Monday when
we do it. a couple more running through
the first three.
>> They were changing. They did a good job.
You know, we we weren't really getting
through on the second level. Some of
their running or their linebackers were
fast over the top. Um and we were
getting picked off and not really being
able to get through. They did a nice
job. Um I thought we were able to loosen
them up with some of the things that we
were able to do that allowed us to run
the football more efficiently in the
latter parts of the game. But you give
them credit. They mix it up. Dinard does
an excellent job of creating a bunch of
issues really that system in general.
and um you know and then they've got
some really good football players across
that front, but a lot of the issues kind
came up from us not being able to get
through on some backside combinations
where their backers were free over the
top.
>> Awesome. Thanks, guys.
this type of performance
team.
>> Yeah, man. I mean, this this is this is
part of it. I think um we obviously
don't want to get satisfied. Like I
think there's some plays out there still
to be made. Um, and you can always grow
and get better. But I mean, this is this
is a good start week two to be, you
know, somewhat rolling like this. Um,
playing, you know, good team football
togetherness. Um, celebrating each
other's success. I mean, it's just it's
the way you dial it up. For sure.
>> Well, I mean, it's it's much more sweet
when you get a double it for sure. I'll
tell you, I've had a few different ones
over the last few years where you know,
you don't it's harder to feel good about
it. So, obviously, it's a little easier
to celebrate it. And um you know, it's
not a literal celebration, but to feel
good about it definitely um it's been a
long career, so it's it's good. Uh
anytime you can be mentioned with, you
know, under a hundred people is just
period of, you know, let alone, you
know, almost top 30 on in in yards.
Like, that's something that means a lot
to me. And um you know I know it means a
lot to my teammates as well because it
means that I'm out there grinding trying
to do what I can do to you know help us
win.
>> Well I got a got singled up a little man
coverage there and um had a a great play
call on. Just had to had to go out there
and win on the on a stutterish go type
route and buckled him a little bit on
the on the route with a little hack and
then got over the top and and and
finished zone on that one. especially
after the first three.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No, he was trying to get me
in that end zone for sure. Um, so it was
good. It was good to finally punch it in
here.
>> Yeah.
>> Philadelphia.
How do you feel that firstatch?
>> Well, I mean, we're not looking at it
like it's a Super Bowl game. I mean, we
attack every game with the same
intentionality and giving them full
respect. Obviously, they're a great
football team, but um I'm not looking at
it like this is the test to see if I've
officially got us over the hump or
anything like that. Um but I'm I'm
excited, man. Anytime you got a a good
opponent, um great opponent. I mean,
they they won a Super Bowl, so
definitely a great team. Um, but anytime
you got a match like that, um, with some
some individual matchups, um, obviously
two really good teams that went really
far, had a chance at it, um, it's
obviously going to be, you know, one
that that we'll feel good about coming
out on the right side
>> after
a big game last week. Did you notice any
kind of shift? Maybe
that has that
first two weeks?
>> Uh, no, not so much. I mean, they Sneeed
still traveled with me and um I mean,
guys kind of it was it was pretty spread
open. It wasn't like I was getting
doubled all game. Um it was there was a
few plays where they where they did
that, but I think they wanted to kind of
slow us down with the shell a little bit
more than doubling or anything crazy
like that. So, um there was
opportunities all you know out there. I
think like I said, we we still had a
couple where um we we could have
potentially come down with it. a couple
questionable situations as far as, you
know, some holdings and stuff like that.
Not to critique the officiating, just
just commenting on the game, but uh but
yeah, we we had a couple opportunities
that we could have even capitalize on a
few more. And that's that's the way we
got to look at it just so we can keep
building, keep getting uh keep getting
better as offense.
>> Y'all love that.
>> What was he telling you about this?
Yeah, I mean he basically like as he
narrated each clip, he just kind of said
this is, you know, we have certain
things in our in our playbook like that
because, you know, the Jets, uh,
Packers, Raiders, when I was there my my
last year, um, similar, you know, uh,
tree that it that it comes from. So, a
lot of the ros that he saw me run is
stuff that obviously, you know, gets run
in this offense as well. So, just
letting me know that, you know, things
that you've been doing marry up great
with with what we do here and can't wait
to see you come over and do it in the in
the Rams uniform. He said that probably
a hundred times in six minutes. So that
was uh that was good.
>> That I mean it has. Yeah. I mean you see
like I said it was we had a couple you
know miscues uh down in the tight red
today where he was trying to get me in
there and so um I'm sure he knew that
that that play was going to score the
one we actually got. So um we didn't
come up with the ones before that but he
just kept kept pushing it trying to you
know get some good calls out there. And
I feel like as we went along throughout
the game, um, he stayed aggressive and,
you know, that's the that's the way you
got to do when you got the type of team
that we have. You know, just going out
there just running the clock out the
whole time. You know, you can do that,
but um, you know, there there's a time
and a place and I like how he called the
game today.
>> You played two games with Stafford so
far? Just what have you seen out of him?
Is there anything you learned about him
being offense?
>> Yeah. Um, to be honest, the most
impressive thing of me watching him
today was his demeanor after he threw
that pick. Just watching how he just I
mean, I told him during the game, I was
like, "Bro, you are just the coolest
dude I've I've been around. Like, just
know, you know, he's not cussing. He's
not blaming anybody. He's just it just
kind of was like it happened in practice
which is I mean you don't you don't want
to have there's obviously another side
to it where you can not care enough but
I mean you could just tell he's dialed
in, locked in, not going to let stuff
like that you know rattle him and um you
know that that kind of radiates
throughout the rest of the team. Just
that type of poise and confidence.
Oh, it was great. Um, missed him once,
rolling to my left. The second one
dropped a snap like a amateur. But, um,
uh, yeah, it was great to get that one
done. We um they brought a zero pressure
all out blitz, felt it, so just tried to
hang in there as long as I could. He
obviously ran a great route. I didn't
get to see the finish of the play, but
seemed like it was in a decent spot and
then he kind of curled in on the inside,
made the play is what I've what I've
been told, but uh he's a hell of a
player. Made some unbelievable catches
today. Connected on some big ones and
and I think there's still more out
there. So, it was great.
>> It's great. Um, you know, Puka obviously
had a great game as well with the
rushing touchdown early kind of set the
tone for us. Um, made some big plays in
the second half on uh one of those first
couple drives which was great for us.
Um, they compliment each other really
well. They both the cool thing is is
cheer for each other. You know, I mean,
nobody's more excited when Tay scores a
touchdown than than Puka and vice versa.
And so, uh, it's just awesome, um, to
have two talented guys that that
compliment each other so well out there.
Imagine
first.
>> Yeah, I mean I think it's a good start,
you know. Um I go back after every game
and there's throws that I want back or
plays that I want back and things
chances that we missed. Um but that's
going to happen and and you got to
continue to try to get better and better
as we do every single week. Um you know,
that's the goal. But, uh, you know, for
the first two games, especially with the
limited time that I had with those two
guys in training camp, I feel good. And,
uh, I just know that they're motivated.
I'm motivated to be as good as we can
possibly be for our team. I mean, that's
what it's all about. Um, you know, so
many guys have a hand in in, uh, us
winning ball games, especially a one
like today where, you know, we handily,
you know, kind of had it there in the
second half. So, uh, just proud of our
team, proud of our defense. Um, really
all the guys up front as well.
>> How are you feeling heading now back to
Philadelphia?
tough loss in the playoffs last year.
>> Should be better weather, I hope. Um,
but uh, no, I mean, they're a good
football team. Um, you know, they've,
uh, you know, retoled and and, um,
brought back a lot of the same people in
a lot of instances as well. So, um, you
know, they got us at our place pretty
pretty handily the first time and then
we gave them a run for their money um,
you know, in the playoffs there. But
really have a ton of respect for their
coach, for their players, um, the way
they go about their business. It'll be a
huge challenge for us. I'm sure it'll be
rocking and rolling.
>> Was just your even that you had after
the interception. Why was that important
for you to show and display that to your
teammates, especially as you guys were
trying to get back on track?
>> Yeah. Um kind of missed me slamming my
helmet, but uh
glad he wasn't looking, but we'll act
like it didn't happen. Um
um but uh no I uh you know I I was I was
pissed at myself because I mean that's
just the one thing you can't do right go
three and out punt it back then give him
a long field but just it was a heck of a
play by Cody Barton guys in the B gap on
you know on the snap of the ball and did
a hell of a job of skating out
underneath it. I didn't think he was
going to get all the way there and made
a great play. Got to give him uh got to
give him credit but uh um yeah I mean
only thing to do is keep playing. I
can't just sit there and you know be
pissed about it all day. Um, you know, I
got to get get mad about it. Figure it
out. I knew exactly right when I left my
hand what the deal was. Okay, well, move
on. And and what's the one thing I can
do? I touched it every play. Let me go
make up for it right now and and play
smart but aggressive in the second half.
And I feel like coach called it that
way. I played it that way and um it
wasn't perfect, but um you know, ended
up in some points, which was good. third
quarter.
It was not the same.
>> It's just execution. Yeah, 100%. It's
execution, right? Um that's what it
boils down to. Obviously got us into a
premier play on the first one uh with
man coverage. Um was able to, you know,
Puka did a great job of winning his
route. Um and then the next play, coach
called a play action pass and they had a
you know a couple backers that were in a
deep spot was able to kind of wiggle one
in there to to Puka as well. But uh it
just it comes down to execution and when
we execute um with the players that we
have and the scheme that we have um we
got a lot, you know, a high probability
of being successful, you know, but it's
it's hard to go execute and that's
defense has a say in it. Everybody's got
a say in it. So um but those four plays
were nice. Um and it was nice to punch
it in. I mean, first half, uh, you know,
drove the ball well a couple times and
and came away with, you know, less than
touchdown, which is frustrating. So, it
was nice to nice to score.
>> Each of the past two weeks, one of the
first things that Sean will say about
you is just how in command you were out
there. Just how would you describe kind
of your base level, just your comfort
level, what you guys are trying to do,
and also the players you have around
you.
>> Yeah, I feel pretty good about it. um
put a lot of time and a lot of effort
into it to trying to make sure that when
we come out here on Sunday that I'm
doing everything I can to make sure that
we're running good football plays into
the good looks and uh those guys
communicate and understand my
communication and we go and we go and we
go play. Um it's not perfect, never is,
but um I definitely, you know, put time
and effort into making sure that we
break the huddle, man. Uh everybody's
locked and loaded and and ready to go
and understanding my plan if you know we
end up changing something. So, um, I
appreciate that, but it's not, uh, you
know, just just hard work and and
frankly a lot of great conversations
with Sean and our coaching staff and and
what we're trying to accomplish on
certain plays and we get certain looks
and hey, can we make this adjustment
here? Can we make this a little bit
better there? What do you think? And
we're just constantly talking about it.
And that's a fun part of the game for
me.
>> Cool. Thanks,
Sweet.
>> What were your first kind of thoughts
about
>> uh I guess it was actually funny. I was
I think I may have said this before, but
it was at Kobe Turner's wedding. I got
that coach McVey called me up. We're on
the dance floor. We're dancing and it's
it's it's Coach McVey. And he's like,
"Hey, what you doing?" I'm like, "Uh,
I'm at Kobe's wedding." He's like, "Uh,
all right. What do you think about
Devonte Adams?" And I'm like, "I think
that would be sweet." Um, I mentioned I'
I grew up a Packers fan, so like uh it
didn't feel real. And then like you
realize we're get there at OTAAS and
you're with him. And uh it's been that
and everything I dreamed of and more. Uh
now we're I'm I just saw on Instagram
where we have a touchdown photo of us
both flexing after his first touchdown
in the Rams. And to be you would have
said that uh when I was in high school,
y'all be like you're crazy. So it it is
pretty awesome.
24.
Yeah, I think it um one it speaks to all
the guys up front of the opportunity for
us to go down field and maybe be able to
make plays and uh I think uh we're all
pretty confident in our guy number nine
and uh his ability to to put it in the
right spot and to absolutely trust uh
with your body that where the ball is
going to be um is a I think an elite um
trait that our team gets to play with as
a wide receiver group because uh of the
confidence that we have in number nine.
>> Speaking of speaking of number nine, I
mean this time in camp and you guys have
had some new players, guys and just
keeps talking about how in command and
comfortable he is. What do you think is
allowing him to just kind of
play this way right now?
>> Yeah, I think um I there there
definitely is a routine that he has the
time and dedication. I know there
there's an opportunity I get in the
mornings to be able to go out there and
watch tape with him. And I know he's
there before I am. And so he's already
dialed up, the notepad's open, he's
writing things down and I'm watching the
clips for the first time and he's like,
"Oh, did you see that up top?" And I'm
like, "Oh, no. I was watching something
else. So, um you know, you know, he's uh
he's put in the time and effort to to
make uh uh our jobs as easy as possible,
but also for his complete understanding.
So, uh uh just yeah, his his routine and
his time is uh it definitely shows out
there on the football field.
>> Yeah. Um it was a yeah a short yardage
call. It's Yeah. During the week, uh
coach says uh get ours and then get
yours. So, it was a it was a get hours
first and I was like, "Holy cow, I'm
still on my feet and I be like, "All
right, let me try to get up out of
here." And, uh, yeah, I think another
another testament to our guys up front
of just the physicality and then I think
especially in our wide receiver room,
it's something that we we pride
ourselves in and then that's something
that Devonte has walked right in and
been a huge part of and uh we asked him
to do a lot as well and uh I know our
guy Jay Wade is always being physical
out there too. So, it's it's an exciting
uh play that uh encompasses our offense.
when you get that call related to you in
the huddle and you know the ball's going
to sit like that like what goes through
your mind
>> uh yeah excitement being like yeah like
yeah you you earn these opportunities to
like have these play calls go to you on
the third down and the short yardage and
uh we we draw it up so yeah I feel like
uh I'm playing uh trying to play the uh
the game and the play before it kind of
goes on watching where the defenders go
and then just trusting it that we got
landmarks and spots where we go and uh
just trusting that our guys will get
that leverage and then Yeah, my foot
ended up on the ground and I was like,
I'm pretty sure I'm standing straight up
right now. So, I was like, let me try to
run this one. So, it worked out.
>> Um, honestly, I don't think so. It was
like like before they were getting like
doing like the daddy the the daddy
daughter dances and stuff. So, it was
like I'm like on the like kind of on the
side and like the music's like playing,
but like nobody's talking. So I'm like
and the only guy talking and I'm like I
like him. I like him a lot.
>> Was that when they were trying to sign
or they already
>> honestly it may have been before. So
yeah it was like it was Yeah, it was it
was uh yeah
I don't know when the wedding was so I
we're going too far back now.
You asked him to lead the individual
drills so that you watch him run
everything like that.
>> Um, shoot. I think some of the stuff
that he does in practice is there's a
lot of clips that I got saved and they
are they are pretty wild and uh it just
goes out. I think of I saw the the
another uh low grabbing low grab he had
today on on the conversion of like I had
that I saw that exact same picture last
week and being like well this kind of
feels like déja vu but I mean you see
him do this stuff during practice. So um
his body control and his understanding
of uh when the when the ball's in the
air how I can go grab it and also just I
think protect himself. That's one thing
uh to see him uh as much as you can when
you're catching some of those balls the
way you land on the ground. Uh there is
a graceful art to it and he's definitely
has established that.
>> Second that the defense has used a
corner to travel with Devonte. What have
you noticed for what that opens up for
you when they focus so much on?
>> Yeah, I think uh it's ability for
everybody out there on the football
field to understand kind of what are
some of the leverages that they're going
to be defense is going to be giving us
and uh I think it gives a lot of
indicators to number nine and the more
information he has uh the better our
offense is going to operate.
>> How do you feel going back to
Philadelphia?
>> Uh Yeah, I think uh it's the next game
ahead of us. It'll be exciting. Yeah,
it's uh it'll be a good opportunity.
We're going to enjoy this win and uh get
back and be ready to be out there this
weekend for sure.